<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">StudyBuddy</string>
    <string name="quiz_name_hint">Name of the quiz</string>
    <string name="quiz_description">Description</string>
    <string name="question_name">Question</string>
    <string name="stats_text">So far you have attempted to solve %1$d quizzes. Doing so, you were asked %2$d questions and answered %3$d of them correctly. That means that you have answered correctly %4$d percent of the time.</string>
    <string name="no_stats_text">You haven\'t played yet!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sample">SampleActivity</string>

    <string name="aboutCardView">
        StudyBuddy is a quiz application that allows you to create your own quiz!\n\n

        StudyBuddy has a lot of categories and has a lots of questions.\n\n
        This app was made using android studio native.\n\n

        This app still has a lot to improve especially the design.\n
        The team will continue developing this application even the final presentation is done.
    </string>

    <string name="theTutorial">
        StudyBuddy can now be your best friend for your upcoming quizzes and exams!
        You can create a quiz by clicking the create button at the bottom.\n\n

        The button below will take to the form that will allow\n you to create unlimited questions!\n
        You can also edit and delete your made quizzes \n on your quiz menu!\n\n

        You can play your quizzes by clicking play at the top.\n\n

        StudyBuddy can now be your best friend for your upcoming quizzes and exams!
        You can create a quiz by clicking the create button at the bottom.\n\n

        The button below will take to the form that will allow\n you to create unlimited questions!\n
        You can also edit and delete your made quizzes \n on your quiz menu!\n\n

        You can play your quizzes by clicking play at the top.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="theTutorialQuizMenu">
        StudyBuddy can now be your best friend for your upcoming quizzes and exams!
        You can create a quiz by clicking the create button at the bottom.\n\n

        1) Create a question by clicking the create button below.\n\n
2) Name the quiz that you want to make.\n\n
3) Create questions for the quiz by clicking add question.\n\n
4) Question field is required to as well as the answers.\n\n
5) You can also create a True or False question by toggling True or false.\n\n
6) You can set the answer as True by toggling the True button (false is the default answer).\n\n
7) When you are done inserting questions for the quiz, you can hit the finish button to finally create the quiz!\n\n

        You can play your quizzes by clicking play at the quiz maker menu.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="gameRulesMath">
        You will be given unlimited math questions before the quiz ends.\n\n

Answer the questions as fast as you can.\n\n

You have 30 seconds to answer all the questions.\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="gameRules">
        You will be given 10 questions based on the category.\n\n

You only have 10 seconds to answer each question.\n\n

The score will depend on how fast you answer the question.\n\n
    </string>
</resources>